runwaysale.co.za 2016-05-20

# Privacy Policy

RUNWAYSALE.co.za, referred to below as RunwaySale, is an online retailer of consumer goods.

RunwaySale values our relationship with you and the other users of this website. We recognize that you may be concerned about our collection, use, and disclosure of your personally identifiable information that we may collect when you use the website. Accordingly, we have implemented this Privacy Policy to inform you of the information that we collect from you, how we collect this information, and what we do with it after we collect it. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us via our [Contact Us](https://www.runwaysale.co.za/contact-us) page.

  * **RunwaySale's Commitment to Online Security**

Your personal information is treated with the greatest of care. Sensitive payment information such as credit card details are NEVER stored with us nor do we have access to them.

  * **How Your Information May Be Shared**

We never sell or rent your personal information. RunwaySale may release personal information under the following circumstances:

Where release is required by law (for example, a subpoena) or regulation or is requested by a government agency;

Where our records indicate a company or an individual may be engaged in fraudulent activity or other deceptive practices that a governmental agency should be made aware of;

To appropriate persons, where your communication suggests possible harm to others.

RunwaySale provides facilities throughout the site to refer friends to RunwaySale. You may not use the "Invite a friend" service or other email forwarding services that we offer to send spam or otherwise send content that would violate our privacy policy or Terms and Conditions. We do not permanently store, sell, or rent these email messages or the email addresses.

Our site's registration form requires you to provide us contact information and may also require demographic information. We may use your contact information from the registration form to send you information about our company. Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary.

You are responsible for all actions taken with your user name, email address and password. Therefore we do not recommend that you disclose your RunwaySale password to any third parties. If you choose to share your username, email address and password or your information with third parties to provide you additional services, you are responsible for all actions taken with this information and therefore you should review that third party's privacy policy.

RunwaySale uses NetCash to provide a secure environment for the authorisation of credit card and charge card transactions. Confidential information including card details are encrypted using industry standard SSL 128-bit encryption technology.

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored in a browser-related file on your computer's hard drive when you use our website. We use cookies to improve the member experience. We also use them to deliver information and fresh content specific to your interests. Cookies are widely used on most major websites. 

While using this website, information about you may be either collected by us or provided by you. Such information will become the property of RunwaySale.

RunwaySale makes use of third-party cookies (including the Google Analytics cookie) to collect website analytics data, and also makes use of third-party cookies (including the DoubleClick cookie) to deliver targeted display advertising to our website visitors based on their browsing and search activity on the RunwaySale website.

No personal information is shared with Google or DoubleClick in order to deliver targeted advertising.

If you prefer not to receive interest-based advertising in web browsers from Google, you can always click the “Opt out” button on the Ads Preferences Manager (<https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/?hl=en>). After you opt out, Google will not collect interest category information and you will not receive interest-based ads via Google when accessing the web through a web browser.

For detail regarding the information Google collects and how it is used to deliver targeted advertising please visit http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/

RunwaySale is not responsible for and gives no warranties or makes any representations in respect of the privacy policies or practices of linked or any third party or advertised web sites.

If you wish to be removed from our database for any reason, simply send us an email requesting to be removed via our [Contact Us](https://www.runwaysale.co.za/contact-us) page.

Updates to our information practices

RunwaySale reserves the right to add to, delete or change these terms because of frequent changes in Internet technology and applicable law. As such, you should check this privacy policy from time to time for such changes.
